cashadvance.com 2015-06-16

# Privacy Policy for Cash Advance®

_This Privacy Policy replaces any privacy policy previously delivered to you or appearing on the CashAdvance.com website, any transaction agreement, or any other document previously delivered to you. If there are conflicts between this Privacy Policy and any other policy delivered to you by CashAdvance.com, the terms of this Privacy Policy shall control until revised. This Privacy Policy is effective as of April 5, 2012._

is Hawk, LLC, which is a limited liability company chartered pursuant to the laws of the Ute Indian Tribe and is wholly owned by enrolled members of the Ute Indian Tribe. By Your use of this website you consent to the laws and jurisdiction of the Ute Indian Tribe as it relates directly or indirectly to your use of this website.

ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND AGREEMENT

CashAdvance.com is not intended for use by individuals under the age of 18 or those who are not legal residents of the United States, United Kingdom or Canada. Please take a moment to review the terms of our Privacy Policy. By using the CashAdvance.com website and participating in any of the CashAdvance.com Services, you agree to accept the terms of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, or if you are not 18 years of age or older and a valid resident of the United States, United Kingdom or Canada, please do not use the CashAdvance.com website or participate in the CashAdvance.com Services.

NOTIFICATION OF CHANGES TO OUR PRIVACY PRACTICES

CashAdvance.com may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. If we make any material changes to our information practices, we will revise this Policy. You are advised to read and review this Policy each and every time you access our website and/or use any service referred to you by CashAdvance.com. Your use of the website constitutes your agreement to the terms of the effective Privacy Policy.

PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION

We collect and combine personally identifiable information (“PII”) and non-personally identifiable information (“Non-PII”) through various sources, including those discussed below. For your reference, PII is data collected with an intention to specifically identify, contact or locate a person, including but not limited to social security number, first name, last name, address, Zip Code, city, state, length of stay at address, whether you rent or own, your e-mail address, driver's license or state ID number, telephone number, work telephone number, time at which you may be contacted, birth date, birth year, whether you are related to someone in the armed forces, whether you make income from job or from benefits, your employer name, duration of employment, employer's phone number, job title, frequency of compensation, your pay dates, your IP address and computer specifications, your ABA/routing number, your bank account number, nature of bank account, name of bank, bank phone number, duration with bank, whether you get paid by direct deposit, monthly net income, and loan amount desired. We may obtain Information about you from third parties such as: credit reports, information about your home and demographic information. We do not pull a credit bureau report on customers without their permission. Conversely, Non-PII is data that is not used to specifically identify, contact or locate an individual, including but not limited to Zip Code, gender, age, or IP address.

ABOUT US

This Privacy Policy is provided to you on behalf of Hawk, LLC, doing business as CashAdvance.com ("CashAdvance.com" or "We" or "Our"). We operate the website located at www.CashAdvance.com, (the "Site"). Through the Site, we operate a prospective customer data base (the "Service"), which compiles, sorts and sells contact information to businesses and networks on behalf of individual consumers who have shown an interest in applying for a business" products or services and have affirmatively asked to be contacted by a representative of a product or service business. We utilize third-party vendors, third-party affiliates, and a variety of media advertisements to promote our Site to consumers interested in using our Site or to supplement our database by purchasing the third-party's database of consumers who have completed applications on websites other than our Site and have affirmatively requested receipt of information about product or service offerings similar to those offered on our Site. Additionally, we advertise third-party services through referrals and/or through pay-per-click advertisements to which you may be redirected through our website. By using the CashAdvance.com website, you agree to our use of your PII and Non-PII for these purposes.

We collect and retain information about you to communicate with you, to process your requests for products and services, and to inform you about other financial services that may be of interest to you through our newsletter. The examples in this Privacy Policy are illustrative only and are not intended to be exclusive.

GLB Act

For purposes of compliance with the Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act, 15 U.S.C. 6802 (the “GLB Act”), this Privacy Policy shall serve as both Your initial customer relationship and annual “Privacy Notice” as defined under the GLB Act. If You would like to opt-out from the disclosure of Your personal information to any third-party for marketing purposes, please visit CashAdvance.com/unsubscribe, enter your email address and click the submit button then confirm your entry.

PATRIOT ACT

Section 326 of the USA PATRIOT ACT requires all financial institutions to obtain, verify, and record information that identifies each person who opens an account or changes an existing account. This federal requirement applies to all new customers and current customers. This information is used to assist the United States government in the fight against the funding of terrorism and money-laundering activities. While CashAdvance.com is not a financial institution, lenders we work with are financial institutions. What this means to you: when you submit information to CashAdvance.com, we will ask for your name, physical address, mailing address, date of birth, and other information that will allow us to identify you. This information will be passed on to the lender that you are matched with on CashAdvance.com. 

OPT-OUT / OPT-IN

We, our affiliate(s) and/or third parties may also promote product and service offerings via e-mail, sms-text message, or telephone to consumers who requested to be contacted either through our Site's online forms Opt-in process or through an Opt-In process on our third-party vendor or affiliate sites ("List Members"). List Members will receive emails, sms-text messages, or telephone contacts for as long as they wish to continue to receive such contacts.

List Members can be removed from our contact lists at any time with no questions asked. To remove your information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service, go to CashAdvance.com/unsubscribe. Or contact us at the email address below:

Please note that participation in certain activities on our Site may be limited if personally identifiable information is not submitted for the user. E-mail addresses and phone numbers received in an opt-out request will be added to our internal Do-Not-Contact registry within ten (10) days following receipt. Unless we hear from you, we will assume you consent to receiving communications from us and our third-party vendors and affiliates.

If a List Member chooses to be removed from our contact list, if applicable, we will also forward this request to the specific third-party vendor or affiliate who provided List Member's informational request to us so that the List Member may be included on the third-party's Do-Not-Contact registry as well. Please bear in mind that if your information was purchased commercially from a third-party vendor or affiliate, CashAdvance.com may not be the only purchaser of your information. Additionally, any third-party vendor or affiliate may have purchased your contact information from an additional third-party and thus you may continue to receive contacts from those third-party companies. CashAdvance.com is not responsible for stopping all unwanted contact from sources beyond our immediate control. We are a CAN-SPAM compliant company.

MINORS

CashAdvance.com does not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 18. No information is knowingly collected from children or used for any purpose whatsoever, including marketing and promotional purposes. If a parent or guardian is made aware that a child under the age of 18 has provided us with personally identifying information through any point of contact, please contact us at the email address below, and we will delete the information about the child referenced from our files.

GENERAL INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE

CashAdvance.com collects information through the Site from our prospective and existing customers at several different points on our Site. We use contact information to send information about our company and to service existing accounts. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the Opt-Out/Opt-In section of this Privacy Policy. Contact and financial information that is collected is used for verifying your name, address and other information. Not all information asked for on our site is required when you fill out our forms. However, the following data is required to use our Site: Social Security number; first name; last name; address; Zip Code; city; state; length of stay at address; whether you rent or own; your e-mail address; driver's license or state ID number; telephone number; work telephone number; time at which you may be contacted; birth date; birth year; IP address or computer hardware specifications; whether you are related to someone in the armed forces; whether you make income from job or from benefits; your employer name; duration of employment; employer's phone number; job title; frequency of compensation; your pay dates; your ABA/routing number; your bank account number; nature of bank account; name of bank; bank phone number; duration with bank; whether you get paid by direct deposit; monthly net income; and loan amount desired. We may obtain Information from third parties about you such as: credit reports, information about your home and demographic information. We do not pull a credit bureau report on customers without their permission.

Information about your computer hardware and software is automatically collected by CashAdvance.com and may be shared in aggregate with third parties whose services are used for traffic-analysis purposes. This information includes: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used by CashAdvance.com to maintain and improve the quality of the service and to generate statistics regarding use of the CashAdvance.com site. CashAdvance.com does not use third party databases to correct or update the information you submit to us for any reason.

COOKIES

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. If a user rejects the cookie, they may still use our site; however, without cookies the user may not have access to certain features on our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. All cookies served on the domain, both session and persistent are tied to the Personally Identifiable Information you provide.

Some of our business partners use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies once set on our site.

LINKS

CashAdvance.com contains links to other sites belonging to third parties. Please be aware that CashAdvance.com is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by CashAdvance.com even in cases where we may frame another site with our own. From time to time, we may co-brand certain services with third-party vendors and affiliates. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting such information and whose privacy statement governs. For example, without limiting the foregoing, we co-brand with insurance brokers, credit reporting agencies and, automotive companies.

SECURITY

We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. For example, we store the personal information you provide on computer systems with limited access, which are located in controlled facilities. When we transmit highly confidential information over the Internet, we protect it through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Socket Layer (SSL) protocol.

DISCLOSURE

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Agreement. By way of example (without limiting the foregoing), we may be forced to disclose information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances as required by law, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access transmissions or private communications.

In addition, as noted above, if you opt-out of future contact from CashAdvance.com by using the opt-out mechanism provided in each e-mail we send to you on behalf of a third- party service provider other than CashAdvance.com, we will provide your email address to the third-party service provider so that the third-party service provider can add your name and contact information to its own Do-Not-Contact list.

As CashAdvance.com develops, we may buy other businesses or their assets or sell our business assets. Customer information is generally one of the business assets involved in such transactions. Thus, in the event that CashAdvance.com or all of its assets are acquired, customer information, including any visitor information collected through the Site, would be one of the transferred assets. For more information see the "Notification of Changes" section of this Privacy Policy.  
Finally, CashAdvance.com reserves the right to disclose member information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) CashAdvance.com's rights or property, other visitors, members, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. CashAdvance.com also reserves the right to disclose visitor or member information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it.

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Site.

SHARING INFORMATION WITH AFFILIATES

When you submit your request for information or quote, you are granting permission to be contacted by CashAdvance.com or affiliated third parties. We share the contact and loan request data you submit on the quote request form and CashAdvance.com account number information with affiliated companies such as, but not limited to, banks, commercial lenders and licensed loan brokers to fulfill information requests we receive from you; to provide you with superior service; inform you of product and service opportunities that may be of interest to you; and for other business purposes. We may disclose all of the information we collect, as described above, to the following types of affiliated companies: financial service providers, such as mortgage and life insurance agencies; title service companies; debt & credit services companies; and auto-finance companies. An "affiliate company" is a company under legal contract with CashAdvance.com to fulfill services or is a company owned in whole or in part by CashAdvance.com or Hawk LLC.

SHARING INFORMATION WITH CO-BRANDED PARTNERS

Some of the services offered on our website are co-branded with contracted partners. Co-branded offerings will be identified directly on the quote request form for the product or service you choose prior to you having to submit the quote request. Where a co-branded product or service provider is identified your Personally Identifiable information will be provided directly to that provider's website. The Product or Service provider shall control your data once submitted to them. For purposes of identification and tracking, your contact information (name, address, phone, e-mail address, etc.) is shared with CashAdvance.com.

We may use personal information to provide the services you've requested, including services that display customized content and advertising. In addition to any fee of which you are notified, your provider's standard messaging rates apply to our confirmation and all subsequent SMS correspondence. You may opt-out and remove your SMS information by sending "STOP," "END," or "QUIT" to the SMS text message you have received. If you remove your SMS information from our database it will no longer be used by us for secondary purposes, disclosed to third parties, or used by us or third parties to send promotional correspondence to you.

FOR CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS

On September 27, 2013, A.B. 370 was signed into law, amending the California Online Privacy Protection Act to require operators of commercial websites like CashAdvance.com to disclose: (1) How CashAdvance.com responds to "Do Not Track” signals; and (2) Whether third parties collect personally identifiable information (PII) about users when they visit CashAdvance.com.

CashAdvance.com does not engage in the collection of personally identifiable information (PII) about an individual consumer’s online activities over time and across third-party Web sites or online services. CashAdvance.com does not honor “do not track” signals. Users who chose to use “do not track” signals will still have access to CashAdvance.com. CashAdvance.com does not permit third parties to collect PII about an individual consumer's online activities over time and across different Web sites when a consumer uses CashAdvance.com. 

DO NOT CONTACT REGISTRY COMPLIANCE

By submitting personal contact and/or financial information, the user hereby grants written permission to CashAdvance.com, its affiliated sites, and its business partners for contact via telephone, mail, and/or e-mail. Further, by registering at CashAdvance.com you are consenting to receive phone calls from CashAdvance.com, its affiliated sites, and its business partners for contact via telephone, including but not limited to lenders that may contact you regarding a loan.

FORMER CUSTOMERS

We treat information about our former customers in the same manner as we treat information about our current customers.

CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We restrict access to nonpublic personal information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with federal standards to guard your nonpublic personal information against unauthorized access or use.  
Maintaining the accuracy of your information is a shared responsibility. We maintain the integrity of the information you provide us and will update your records when you notify us of a change. Please contact us at the address or phone number listed below when information concerning you changes.

SITE AND SERVICE UPDATES

We will send the user site and service announcement updates. Members are not able to unsubscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the service. We also communicate with user to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to the account via e-mail or telephone when requested.

CORRECT / UPDATE INFORMATION

If you would like to verify any data that we have received from you, make any corrections or disable the use of your personal information, please log into your account here on cashadvance.com, or contact us at: 

CHOICE OF LAW AND CHOICE OF FORUM

The Ute Tribe of Utah is a federally recognized Indian Tribe, and as such, the Tribe and its chartered companies, including Hawk, LLC, are not subject to civil suit in any forum whatsoever absent an express waiver of sovereign immunity. In the event of any dispute or conflict which may arise between You and Your use of Our Website You hereby agree that the laws of the Ute Tribe of Utah shall govern any and all disputes or conflicts, without regard to conflict of law provisions and any disputes shall be brought solely in the tribal courts of the Ute Ouray Reservation of Utah. In addition, the terms and practices described in this Privacy Policy will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the Ute Tribe of Utah, without regard to conflict of law provisions. Neither Your use of Our Website nor anything herein shall be construed or deemed a waiver, impliedly or otherwise, of sovereign immunity.

INFORMATION FOR ISPs

Website: CashAdvance.com  
Company Name: Hawk, LLC  
c/o Capital Management  
3315 HWY 50, Silver Springs  
NV 89429  
Phone Number: (800) 590-0078  
Email: 

CashAdvance.com understands the importance of protecting consumers’ personal information and the proper use of their personal information. It is Our policy to not send unsolicited e-mails to consumers and we hope the following information will eliminate any concerns that Your company may have regarding Our practices of consumers’ personal information.

CashAdvance.com and its affiliated sites use only an “opt-in or opt-out” method of obtaining customer information. All personal information from consumers is obtained voluntarily from the consumer. We obtain personal information from third parties that follow the same set of policies.

All e-mail communications sent by us to consumers include information about the origin of the e-mail and include easily identifiable instructions on how consumers can unsubscribe from receiving future e-mail messages from us. Below is an example of e-mail communications sent by us to subscribers.

________________________________________

This e-mail is not sent unsolicited. This is a CashAdvance.com emailing. Offers are sent to subscribers ONLY.

To be removed from Our list, click here.

View Our Privacy Policy.

ISPs view Our policies.

________________________________________

In some instances, CashAdvance.com will enter into a Privacy Policy with a third-party website to allow consumers to opt-in to our marketing program on those third party websites. When this occurs we make certain that the third-party websites represent and warrant to us that the consumer data was collected voluntarily by consumer registration and/or co-registrations. We also require that the third-party websites have a right under any applicable privacy policy to transfer the consumer data to us, and that CashAdvance.com has the right to send marketing offers to the consumer.

We hope this information satisfies any questions or concerns you may have as an ISP regarding our e-mail practices. If you have additional questions or wish to discuss the matter further, please contact us at .
